{
    "data_info": {
        "documentID": "J_FOOD_055016",
        "source": "도서",
        "writer": "노중훈",
        "ISBN_ISNN": "978-89-5277-759-1",
        "version": "초판",
        "source_language": "ko",
        "translator": "파파고",
        "source_url": "식당 골라주는 남자",
        "collectedDate": "2023-11-03",
        "publishedDate": "2016-12-25",
        "domain": "음식점",
        "title": "OR COFFEE"
    },
    "text": "/ブラウンチーズクロッフルダブル、14,000ウォン/イチゴクロッフルシングル、9,000ウォン/イチゴクロッフルダブル、16,000ウォン/イチゴクロッフルケーキ、24,000ウォン/チーズケーキ、5,000ウォン/ブルーベリーケーキ、5,500ウォン/レモンパイ、6,000ウォン/緑茶クリームオロル、6,000ウォン/クッキー、2,500ウォン/生クリームプリンティング·6,000ウォン/ミニトースト·3,500ウォン/ベーグル·4,500ウォン /一口サンドイッチ·6,500ウォン / アイスクリーム,500ウォン /クッキーミルク·4,500ウォン。",
    "QA": [
        {
            "question": "ブラウンチーズクロッフルダブルの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ブラウンチーズクロッフルダブルは14,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "イチゴクロッフルシングルの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "イチゴクロッフルシングルは9,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "イチゴクロッフルダブルの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "イチゴクロッフルダブルは16,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "イチゴクロッフルケーキの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "イチゴクロッフルケーキは24,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "チーズケーキの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "チーズケーキは5,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "ブルーベリーケーキの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ブルーベリーケーキは5,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "レモンパイの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "レモンパイは6,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "緑茶クリームオロルの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "緑茶クリームオロルは6,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "クッキーの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "クッキーは2,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "生クリームプリンティングの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "生クリームプリンティングは6,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "ミニトーストの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ミニトーストは3,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "ベーグルの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "ベーグルは4,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "一口サンドイッチの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "一口サンドイッチは6,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "アイスクリームの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "アイスクリームは500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "クッキーミルクの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "クッキーミルクは4,500ウォンです。"
        }
    ],
    "word_Count": {
        "text": 206,
        "QA": 438
    }
}